<core:FragmentDefinition xmlns="sap.m"
	xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:u="sap.ui.unified" xmlns:tnt="sap.tnt"
	height="100%" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<Panel>
		<content>

			<html:h4 align="center">Super Efficient Ceiling Fan DSM Programme
			</html:h4>
			<html:h4 align="center">Programme Details</html:h4>
			<html:ol>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Eligibility:</html:b>
						The programme is available for Residential category consumers of
						Tata Power in the Mumbai License Area.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Program partner:</html:b>
						Tata Power has partnered with Atomberg Technologies Private
						Limited (M/S Atomberg) which will offer the super efficient
						ceiling fans under this programme.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Product Details:</html:b>
						The product offered is Atomberg Make , Energy efficient Fan of
						1200 mm Size. Please click on Product Details for more
						information.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Number of Ceiling Fans per consumer:</html:b>
						Each consumer is eligible to purchase upto 4 ceiling fans under
						the programme.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Warranty:</html:b>
						The ceiling fans purchased under this programme, will have 3 years
						warranty, which will be provided by manufacturer
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Offer price:</html:b>The
						ceiling fans are offered under New Purchase Scheme . The products
						and offer price may change without giving prior notice. (Please
						click on 'Models Available' tab to view the price). includes all
						taxes &amp; duties and three years warranty. The price doesn't
						include installation of ceiling fans.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Registration </html:b>
						Web-site:-For registration please click on the "Register Here"
						tab, read and accept the terms and conditions and submit the
						details. A unique registration number will be displayed after the
						successful registration.
						Call centre:-Consumer can also register by calling the Tata Power Call
						Centre 1800-209-5161
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Order confirmation</html:b>
						A representative of the authroised franchisee of Atomberg will
						contact you on the phone number provided by you and confirm the
						models and colour required and confirm the order.
					</html:h5>

				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Payment</html:b>
						Consumer can make the payment through a)Online payment facility
						b)Cheque/DD and c)Cash Atomberg Installation agency will provide
						all the details and receipt for the payment.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Role of Tata Power:</html:b>
						Tata Power has rolled out this programme to help consumers to save
						the energy. Tata Power is offering a special rebate to bring the
						effective price down for the consumers. Tata Power is only a
						facilitator and all product related issues/ disputes/ differences
						shall be referred to the manufacturer directly by the customer
						without any liability, financial or otherwise, on Tata Power.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
			</html:ol>

		</content>
	</Panel>
</core:FragmentDefinition>