<core:FragmentDefinition xmlns="sap.m" xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:u="sap.ui.unified" xmlns:tnt="sap.tnt" height="100%"
	xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<Panel >
		<content>
			<html:div class="container-fluid">
				<html:div class="go-green_intro audit_prog">
					<html:div class="row intro_head">
						<html:div class="col-xs-12">
							<html:div class="faq_bg border_rad_icon">
								<html:div class="row icon_row_flex">
									<html:div class="col-xs-2">
										<html:image src="images/icon_calulator.png" alt="icon_calulator" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
									</html:div>
									<html:div class="col-xs-10">
										<html:h4>Energy Saving</html:h4>
									</html:div>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
				</html:div>
				<html:div class="energy_saving_desc">
					<html:div class="row">
						<html:div class="col-sm-3 text-center">
							<html:image src="images/mumbai.jpg" alt="mumbai" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
						</html:div>
						<html:div class="col-sm-9">
							<html:p>
								Mumbai is the one Indian city that has always enjoyed uninterrupted, 24-hour power supply. Something that we in Mumbai are rightly proud of.
								However, following the severe power shortage faced by State of Maharashtra and the city's unprecedented lifestyle boom, this envied status
								of uninterrupted power is under threat. While efforts are on to plug the power deficit of 400-500 MW in Mumbai through alternate resources,
								with summer around the corner, we could be in for a power shortage crisis during the peak hours of 10 am - 8 pm.
							</html:p>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
					<html:div class="row">
						<html:div class="col-sm-12">
							<html:p>
								But it doesn't have to be that way, if we act now. A few simple steps and we can avoid power cuts. But before we list out those steps, just
								ask yourself, "Am I willing to do my bit for the future of our great city?" I think we all know the answer.
							</html:p>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
					<html:div class="row">
						<html:div class="col-sm-12">
							<html:h4>Shift consumption away from the 10 am - 8 pm peak times:</html:h4>
							<html:p>
								Let's avoid adding to the power demand during this peak time. By simply using some of our common electrical appliances before and after this
								time band. Washing machines, geysers, irons, water pumps in buildings - all can be shifted without much inconvenience.
							</html:p>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
					<html:div class="row">
						<html:div class="col-sm-12">
							<html:h4>ACs at 26º C</html:h4>
							<html:p>
								ACs are possibly the biggest cause of any summer power crisis. Every time one more AC is switched on and every time the temperature is
								lowered by one more degree, a huge load is added to the system. We can however work towards uninterrupted power - if we give up 'freezing'
								for 'cool enough'. Let's all go 26 this summer - it's actually quite comfortable.
							</html:p>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
					<html:div class="row">
						<html:div class="col-sm-12">
							<html:h4>Switch off from the plug point</html:h4>
							<html:p>
								Whenever we leave a plug point 'ON' after switching an electrical appliance 'OFF' with the remote, power is still being consumed in
								'stand-by mode'. And no small amount either - these little wastages account for an unbelievable 5% of the city's power consumption. You will
								agree that's a sheer waste. So, after usage, let's switch off our ACs, TVs, washing machines, microwaves, geysers and mobile chargers from
								the plug point. Every single time. It is up to each one of us to make the change - if you will, Mumbai will!
							</html:p>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
					<html:div class="row">
						<html:div class="col-sm-12">
							<html:h4>Save Electricity</html:h4>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Light</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Switch off lights and fans when not required.</html:li>
										<html:li>Replace bulbs with tube lights &amp; CFL(Compact Flourescent Lamps).</html:li>
										<html:li>Utilise natural light by using electronic chokes &amp; regulators instead of conventional copper chokes.</html:li>
										<html:li>Optimise use of lights in malls, multiplexes &amp; hotels.</html:li>
										<html:li>Turn off the lights when not in use.</html:li>
										<html:li>Take advantage of daylight by using light-coloured, loose-weave curtains on your windows to allow daylight to penetrate the room.
											Also, decorate with lighter colours that reflect daylight.</html:li>
										<html:li>De-dust lighting fixtures to maintain illumination.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use task lighting; instead of brightly lighting an entire room, focus the light where you need it.</html:li>
										<html:li>Compact fluorescent bulbs are four times more energy efficient than incandescent bulbs and provide the same lighting.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="col-sm-4 text-center">
									<html:image src="images/enrg_sav_bulb.jpg" alt="enrg_sav_bulb" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Electric iron</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Select iron boxes with automatic temperature cutoff.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use appropriate regulator position for ironing.</html:li>
										<html:li>Do not put more water on clothes while ironing.</html:li>
										<html:li>Do not iron wet clothes.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="col-sm-4 text-center">
									<html:image src="images/engr_sav_iron.jpg" alt="engr_sav_iron" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Fans</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Replace conventional regulators with electronic regulators for ceiling fans.</html:li>
										<html:li>Install exhaust fans at a higher elevation than ceiling fans.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Refrigerator</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Do not open door frequently.</html:li>
										<html:li>Set thermostat in medium cooling position.</html:li>
										<html:li>Keep adequate space from wall.</html:li>
										<html:li>Do not overload the refrigerator.</html:li>
										<html:li>Defrost your refrigerator regularly.</html:li>
										<html:li>Regularly defrost manual-defrost refrigerators and freezers; frost buildup increases the amount of energy needed to keep the motor running.</html:li>
										<html:li>Leave enough space between your refrigerator and the walls so that air can easily circulate around the refrigerator.</html:li>
										<html:li>Don't keep your refrigerator or freezer too cold.</html:li>
										<html:li>Make sure your refrigerator door seals are airtight.</html:li>
										<html:li>Cover liquids and wrap foods stored in the refrigerator. Uncovered foods release moisture and make the compressor work harder.</html:li>
										<html:li>Do not open the doors of the refrigerators frequently.</html:li>
										<html:li>Don't leave the fridge door open for longer than necessary, as cold air will escape.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use smaller cabinets for storing frequently used items.</html:li>
										<html:li>Avoid putting hot or warm food straight into the fridge.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="col-sm-4 text-center">
									<html:image src="images/enrg_sav_refrigerator.jpg" alt="enrg_sav_refrigerator" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Washing Machine</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Use after 10 PM or before 10 AM.</html:li>
										<html:li>Run washing machine only with full load.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use the shortest cycle time.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use optimal quantity of water.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use timer facility to save energy.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use the correct amount of detergent.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use hot water only for very dirty clothes.</html:li>
										<html:li>Always use cold water in the rinse cycle.</html:li>
										<html:li>Prefer natural drying over electric dryers.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="col-sm-4 text-center">
									<html:image src="images/enrg_sav_washing_machine.jpg" alt="enrg_sav_washing_machine" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Geyser</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Use before 10 AM.</html:li>
										<html:li>Switch off when not required.</html:li>
										<html:li>Reduce thermostat setting from 60º to 50º C.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use Solar Water Heater - a good replacement for an electric water heater.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="col-sm-4 text-center">
									<html:image src="images/enrg_sav_geyser.jpg" alt="enrg_sav_geyser" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Mixers</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Avoid dry grinding in your food processors (mixers and grinders) as it takes longer time than liquid grinding.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Microwave Ovens</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Use these appliances to reduce energy consumption by 50 % compared to conventional electric / gas stoves.</html:li>
										<html:li>Do not bake large food items.</html:li>
										<html:li>Unless you're baking breads or pastries, you may not even need to preheat.</html:li>
										<html:li>Don't open the oven door too often to check food condition as each opening leads to a temperature drop of 25º C.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="col-sm-4 text-center">
									<html:image src="images/enrg_sav_kitchen.jpg" alt="enrg_sav_kitchen" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Electric Stove</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Turn off electric stoves several minutes before the specified cooking time.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use flat-bottomed pans that make full contact with the cooking coil.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Gas Stove</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>When cooking on a gas burner, use moderate flame settings to conserve LPG.</html:li>
										<html:li>Remember that a blue flame means your gas stove is operating efficiently.</html:li>
										<html:li>Yellowish flame is an indicator that the burner needs cleaning.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use pressure cookers as much as possible.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use lids to cover the pans while cooking.</html:li>
										<html:li>Bring items taken out of refrigerators (like vegetable, milk, etc.) to room temperature before placing on the gas stove for heating.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-8">
									<html:h5>Air Conditioning</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="inti_list">
										<html:li>Ensure proper sealing of doors and windows.</html:li>
										<html:li>Set thermostat at 24º C for optimum cooling.</html:li>
										<html:li>Clean AC filter every month.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use film / tinted glass on windows.</html:li>
										<html:li>Prefer air conditioners having automatic temperature cut off.</html:li>
										<html:li>Keep regulators at "low cool" position.</html:li>
										<html:li>Operate the ceiling fan in conjunction with your window air conditioner to spread the cooled air more effectively throughout the
											room and operate the air conditioner at higher temperature.</html:li>
										<html:li>Seal the doors and windows properly.</html:li>
										<html:li>Leave enough space between your air conditioner and the walls to allow better air circulation.</html:li>
										<html:li>A roof garden can reduce the load on Air Conditioner.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use windows with sun films / curtains.</html:li>
										<html:li>Set your thermostat as high as comfortably possible in the summer. The less difference between the indoor and outdoor temperatures,
											the lower will be energy consumption.</html:li>
										<html:li>Don't set your thermostat at a colder setting than normal when you turn on your air conditioner. It will not cool your home any
											faster and could result in excessive cooling.</html:li>
										<html:li>Don't place lamps or TV sets near your air-conditioning thermostat. The thermostat senses heat from these appliances, which can
											cause the air conditioner to run longer than necessary.</html:li>
										<html:li>Plant trees or shrubs to shade air-conditioning units but not to block the airflow. A unit operating in the shade uses as much as
											10% less electricity than the same one operating in the sun.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="col-sm-4 text-center">
									<html:image src="images/enrg_sav_ac.jpg" alt="enrg_sav_ac" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
				</html:div>
			</html:div>
		</content>
	</Panel>
</core:FragmentDefinition>