<core:FragmentDefinition xmlns="sap.m" xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:u="sap.ui.unified" xmlns:tnt="sap.tnt" height="100%"
	xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<Panel >
		<content>
			<html:div class="go-green_intro">
				<html:div class="row intro_head">
					<html:div class="col-xs-12">
						<html:div class="faq_bg border_rad_icon">
							<html:div class="row icon_row_flex">
								<html:div class="col-xs-2">
									<html:image src="images/icon_calulator.png" alt="icon_calulator" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="col-xs-10">
									<html:h4>Power Failure Problem</html:h4>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
				</html:div>
			</html:div>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false" headerText="Why do I face power failures?" width="auto" class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>Power reaches to you from substation through line or cable. At your end power supply is fed through cut-outs / fuses installed in
							your house or in your building near your meter. Power failure occurs most commonly due to blown fuse or due to cable damage. The fuse may
							blow due to short-circuit or overloading of equipment. Further in spite of our best efforts to provide uninterrupted power, there could be
							problem in the line or in cable between substation and powerhouse due to storms or falling of trees.</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false" headerText="How do I report a power failure?" width="auto" class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							In the event of any Power Failures, you can register a Power Failure complaint via SMS. Send NS &lt;12 digit Consumer No&gt; to 9223170707.
							You can also register a complaint by logging into our Mobile App Or by sending us a Whatsapp at 7045116237
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false" headerText="How often do I need to follow up after reporting of power failure?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>Once power failure has been reported there is no need to report again. Quickly Tata Power personnel start working on the problem.
							Although we make all possible efforts to get all customers back online as quickly as possible, the actual time required to restore power may
							vary depending upon nature of failure. You may ask Call Centre to provide estimated time of restoration. Call Centre will provide this
							information once the problem is identified. If power is not restored within few hours or your neighbor's power has come back but yours is
							still off, you may contact Call Centre again to get the latest status on power restoration.</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false" headerText="Why do my neighbours have power and mine is still off?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							In case of residential customers, if your neighbours have power supply when you don't, the fault is most probably within your house. It is
							advisable to call the local electrician in such cases.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false" headerText="Can I use a portable generator during non-availability of power supply?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>Residential customer can use Gen Set in their house during power outage or failure. However commercial and industrial customers
							require separate permission to do so. However generator should be connected after isolating main supply through a double throw switch to
							break main circuit before Gen Set circuit is made. It should never be plugged or connected to main supply inlet in the house. If it is
							connected in the same circuit, electricity will travel through power line or transformer, creating mortal danger to utility personnel
							working on the line. This switch is also required to protect Gen Set and appliances in your house when regular power supply is restored.</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false" headerText="Can I switch ON all the appliances once the power is resumed?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:ul>
							<html:li>
								<html:h5>
									As a precautionary measure, when power supply fails one should switch OFF the critical equipment such as air-conditioners, PCs,
									Refrigerators, Television sets , etc. Please do not forget to switch OFF Geyser.
								</html:h5>
							</html:li>
							<html:li>
								<html:h5>
									When the power is resumed, it is recommended to switch ON the appliances one by one. After prolonged outage of power supply, please check
									food stored in your refrigerator for signs of spoilage. Don't take a chance on food if you are not sure.
								</html:h5>
							</html:li>
						</html:ul>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="Why are there voltage fluctuations? Who should we contact if we get low / high voltage?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							Tata Power is a part of Western regional power grid along with other utilities such as MSEB, BSES, GSEB, MPEB etc. Any disturbance in this
							western grid results into voltage fluctuation for a very short duration and is beyond the control of Tata Power. We take every care to avoid
							such disturbances and also try to restrict their duration and effect.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
		</content>
	</Panel>
</core:FragmentDefinition>