<core:FragmentDefinition xmlns="sap.m"
	xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:u="sap.ui.unified" xmlns:tnt="sap.tnt"
	height="100%" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<Panel>
		<content>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="What is Refrigerator exchange programme?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							Under DSM (Demand Side Management) , Tata Power has
							initiated several programs to promote energy efficiency at
							consumer premises and the programs are approved by MERC
							(Maharashtra Electricity Regulatory Commission). The program
							objective is to reduce electricity consumption and enhance energy
							efficiency. The program is launched by Tata Power in tie up with
							CROMA (Infiniti Retail Ltd) and Godrej (Godrej and Boyce
							Manufacturing Company Ltd). Currently, the program is offered to
							Residential Consumers of Tata Power in Mumbai License Area. Under
							this program the eligible consumer gets an opportunity to replace
							their inefficient old refrigerator with new energy efficient
							refrigerator, which is expected to reduce power consumption
							thereby reducing their electricity bill in long run. New purchase
							without exchange option is also made available. Tata Power has
							negotiated a bulk discount with the Manufacturer and Tata Power
							is also contributing subsidy amount to offer the energy efficient
							products to consumers at a large discount.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="Which type of models are selected under the programme ?"
				width="auto" class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							Direct Cool (single door) and Frost Free (double door)
							models upto 300 liter capacity having latest BEE 5 star rating
							are selected under this program.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="Which are the Models available and what are the costs?"
				width="auto" class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							The available models and price can be seen under tab
							"Models Available". The Models and prices may change without
							prior notice.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="What is the Maximum capacity?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							TUnder this programme, the models available are upto 300
							Liter capacity.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="How many Refrigerator I can get under this programme?"
				width="auto" class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							Each eligible consumer can purchnase ONE refrigerator
							under this programme.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="What will you do with the old refrigerator?"
				width="auto" class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							The old refrigerator collected from consumer would be
							scrapped in an environmental friendly manner.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="What would be Warranty of this Refrigerator?"
				width="auto" class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							Standard ONE year refrigerator Warranty and 5 years
							compressor warranty is offered by the manufacturers.Some models
							are having 10 years compressor warranty. Additional refrigerator
							warranty of 1 year is offered at extra cost.


						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="What shall I do in case of defect in the Refrigerator?"
				width="auto" class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							Consumer can register the complaint to manufacturer as
							per Warranty card issued to consumer.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="How do I participate in the programme?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							<html:b>Registration</html:b>
							Web-site:- For registration please click on the "Register Here"
							tab, read and accept the terms and conditions and submit the
							details. A unique registration number will be displayed after the
							successful registration.
						</html:h5>
						<html:h5>
							<html:b>Order processing</html:b>
							Program partner will contact the consumer on registered contact
							number. He will provide necessary information regarding available
							products and confirm the order. He will also advice about the
							payment methodology. The new refrigerator will be delivered only
							at the residential address mentioned on the consumer's
							electricity bill. In case of exchange, the old refrigerator will
							also be picked up only from the residential address mentioned on
							the consumer's electricity bill.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="What are the documents which will be required at the time of installation?"
				width="auto" class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							Consumer will be required to provide copy of latest Tata
							Power Electricity Bill and Programme registration number.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="What is the role of Tata Power?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							Tata Power has rolled out the programme and offered
							special rebate to help the consumers to replace their inefficient
							appliance by new energy efficient appliance. Tata Power is only a
							facilitator of this Programme and its role &amp; liability is
							restricted only to offering a rebate to the manufacturer. The
							Warranty for the product is provided by manufacturer and any
							future issue regarding product, installation and Warranty etc.
							shall be directly dealt with manufacturer without involving Tata
							Power. Tata Power shall not be responsible in any manner
							(financial or otherwise) for any issues relating to this
							Programme or the product in future. Tata Power's decision in all
							respects for issues/ disputes/differences shall be final.
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			<Panel expandable="true" expanded="false"
				headerText="Whom should I contact in case of query?" width="auto"
				class="sapUiResponsiveMargin">
				<content>
					<html:div class="textpara">
						<html:h5>
							       In case of any query you can contact

							<html:a href="mailto:dsmcell@tatapower.com">dsmcell@tatapower.com</html:a>
						</html:h5>
					</html:div>
				</content>
			</Panel>
			
			
		</content>
	</Panel>
</core:FragmentDefinition>