<core:FragmentDefinition xmlns="sap.m"
	xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:u="sap.ui.unified" xmlns:tnt="sap.tnt"
	height="100%" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<Panel>
		<content>

			<html:h4 align="center">Energy Efficient Refrigerator New Purchase &amp;
				Exchange Programme
			</html:h4>
			<html:h5>Dear Consumer,</html:h5>

			<html:p>
				Thanks for your interest in our DSM 5 Star Refrigerator New Purchase and
				Exchange programme.

				Here is a chance to bring the energy efficiency to an appliance which
				works 24X7.

				A whooping discount upto 40% on MRP is provided on the products in
				this programme.

				This phase of the programme offers many benefits including multiple
				brands, wide range of models,
				more purchase options, choice of warranty period and others.

				This programme is open for new purchase and exchange basis.

				Models offered under this program comply with the latest BEE 5 Star rating
				of energy efficiency.
			</html:p>
			<html:ol>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Eligibility:</html:b>
						The programme is available for Residential category consumers of
						Tata Power in the Mumbai License Area.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Type and Capacity:</html:b>
						Wide range of models upto 300 Litres of net capacity.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Implementation partners:</html:b>
						Infiniti Retail Limited (Croma) and Godrej and Boyce Manufacturing
						Company Ltd (Godrej).
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Number of Refrigerators per consumer:</html:b>
						1 Number
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Warranty:</html:b>
						One Year Refrigerator Warranty and 5/10 years of compressor
						warranty.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Extended Warranty:</html:b>
						The
						A consumer can avail 1 year extended warranty by paying the
						additional price.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Buyback of old Refrigerators:</html:b>
						A consumer has to surrender his old refrigerator in working
						condition under the exchange option.
						Old refrigerator will be
						scrapped in the ecofriendly manner. Buyback
						price is included in
						the offer price.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Offer price:</html:b>
						Offer price given in the table on website includes all taxes,
						duties, buyback of old refrigerator and delivery charges.
						Offer
						price may be change without any prior notice. The consumers who
						do
						not have old refrigerator or do not want to exchange old
						refrigerator, may opt for new purchase by paying Rs.1000 extra.
					</html:h5>

				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Registration</html:b>
						a. Website:- Consumer can register online by visiting our webpage,
						'BE GREEN' at
						<html:a> www.tatapower.com. </html:a>
						b. Call Center:- Consumer can also register by dialing our call
						center at 1800 209 5161
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Order Confirmation and Delivery:</html:b>
						Post registration, vendor will contact/visit the consumer to
						provide further details
						for confirmation of the order. Vendor will
						also provide necessary
						information about payment methodology and
						delivery.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Payment Methodology:</html:b>
						Multiple Online/Card payment options will be made available by the
						vendor.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
				<html:li>
					<html:h5>
						<html:b>Role of Tata Power:</html:b>
						Tata Power has rolled out this programme to help consumers to save
						the energy. Tata Power is offering a special rebate to bring the
						effective cost down for the consumers. Tata Power is only a
						facilitator and all product related issues/ disputes/ differences
						shall be referred to the manufacturer directly by the customer
						without any liability, financial or otherwise, on Tata Power.
					</html:h5>
				</html:li>
			</html:ol>
			<html:h4 align="center">
				For any query, please write to
				<html:a href="mailto:dsmcell@tatapower.com">dsmcell@tatapower.com</html:a>
			</html:h4>
		</content>
	</Panel>
</core:FragmentDefinition>