<mvc:View xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:mvc="sap.ui.core.mvc" xmlns="sap.m" controllerName="tatapower.dev.controller.ReducingyourBill"
	xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<App>
		<pages>
			<Page showNavButton="true" navButtonPress="onNavBack" showHeader="false">
				<content>
					<core:Fragment fragmentName="tatapower.dev.fragments.Main.HeaderMain" type="XML"/>
					<core:Fragment fragmentName="tatapower.dev.fragments.Main.HeaderMenu" type="XML"/>
					<html:div class="container">
						<Panel>
							<html:div class="container-fluid">
								<html:div class="go-green_intro">
									<html:div class="row intro_head">
										<html:div class="col-xs-12">
											<html:div class="grn_cor border_rad_icon">
												<html:div class="row icon_row_flex">
													<html:div class="col-xs-2">
														<html:image src="images/icon_green_corn.png" alt="icon_green_corn" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
													</html:div>
													<html:div class="col-xs-10">
														<html:h4>Reducing Your Bill</html:h4>
													</html:div>
												</html:div>
											</html:div>
										</html:div>
									</html:div>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="green_build_desc">
									<html:p>
										Energy conservation and reducing bills should become a mantra to be competitive for everyone. The way one would exercise every day, we
										recommend our customers to reflect on some simple solutions and options that can be implemented without any specialised support. It's proven
										that as high as 10 to 15% of savings can come through no-cost or low-cost options evolving from changing operational practices.
									</html:p>
									<html:p>
										If you are on a two-part tariff, one basic component of your bill is the demand charge. Options available for an industrial consumer is to
										identify processes that run simultaneously but are not essential for the main production. Such processes should be operated in series as
										against in parallel to save on the total demand. Example - if you are running baking ovens in a particular shift and are also running large
										dryers during the same shift, you can always, change the shift operations to run the two processes in series instead of parallel. Other
										example - if you pump water from municipal source to overhead tanks, try and run the pumps during the time when main process is not
										operational. This will save total demand.
									</html:p>
									<html:p>
										Watch your bills and study if you are paying power factor penalty. If you are, assess the benefit-cost of installing capacitor banks or
										Automatic Power Factor Correction panels and savings due to reduced power factor penalty.
									</html:p>
									<html:h5>
										Power Consumption Guidelines
									</html:h5>
									<html:p>
										Use the Ready Reckoner on
										<html:strong>Power Consumption Guideline</html:strong>
										to know units consumed per month for appliances/equipment based on usage pattern.
									</html:p>
									<html:h5>
										Energy Calculator
									</html:h5>
									<html:p>
										We recommend you to use the interactive
										<html:strong>Energy Calculator</html:strong>
										to know your electricity bill based on your consumption pattern. Use the calculator to also simulate how much you can save if you reduce
										hours of usage per day for some of the appliances/equipment.
									</html:p>
									<html:h5>
										Energy Savings Tips
									</html:h5>
									<html:p>
										We recommend you to visit some simple but proven and
										<html:strong>effective tips</html:strong>
										to save electricity consumption. Tata Power will keep on adding more tips for your benefit.
									</html:p>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
						</Panel>
					</html:div>
					<core:Fragment fragmentName="tatapower.dev.fragments.Main.Footer" type="XML"/>
				</content>
			</Page>
		</pages>
	</App>
</mvc:View>