<mvc:View xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:mvc="sap.ui.core.mvc" xmlns="sap.m" controllerName="tatapower.dev.controller.TermOfUse"
	xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<App>
		<pages>
			<Page title="Terms of Use" showNavButton="true" navButtonPress="onNavBack" showHeader="false">
				<content>
					<core:Fragment fragmentName="tatapower.dev.fragments.Main.HeaderMain" type="XML"/>
					<core:Fragment fragmentName="tatapower.dev.fragments.Main.HeaderMenu" type="XML"/>
					<html:div class="container">
						<html:div class="terms_of_use">
							<html:h4 class="text-center">
								Tata Power - Terms of Use
							</html:h4>
						</html:div>
						<html:div class="tou_desc">
							<html:p>
								This Website will be provided by TATA POWER, and may be used for informational purposes only. By using the site or downloading materials
								from the site, you agree to abide by the terms and conditions set forth in this notice. If you do not agree to abide by these terms and
								conditions please do not use the site or download materials from the site.
							</html:p>
							<html:h5>LIMITED LICENSE</html:h5>
							<html:p>
								Subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement, TATA POWER will grant a non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited right to
								access this site and the materials thereon. You agree not to:
							</html:p>
							<html:ul class="inti_list">
								<html:li>Interrupt or attempt to interrupt the operation of the Site in any way.</html:li>
								<html:li>Intrude or attempt to intrude into the site in any way.</html:li>
								<html:li>Post any obscene, defamatory or annoying materials on the site.</html:li>
								<html:li>Obscure any materials, including this notice, already posted on the site.</html:li>
								<html:li>Use the site or any contents thereof to defame, intimidate, annoy or otherwise cause nuisance or breach the rights of any person.</html:li>
							</html:ul>
							<html:p>
								TATA POWER authorises to view and download the information ("Materials") at this Website ("Site") only for personal, non-commercial use.
								This authorization is not a transfer of title in the Materials and copies of the Materials and is subject to the following restrictions:
							</html:p>
							<html:ul class="inti_list">
								<html:li>Retain, on all copies of the Materials downloaded, all copyright, trademarks and other proprietary notices contained in the
									Materials, consent.</html:li>
								<html:li>Not modify the Materials in any way nor reproduce or display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or
									commercial purpose.</html:li>
								<html:li>Not transfer the Materials to any other person unless you give them notice of, and they agree to accept, the obligations arising
									under these terms and conditions of use. You agree to abide by all additional restrictions displayed on the Site as it may be updated from
									time to time. This Site, including all Materials, is copyrighted and protected by worldwide copyright laws and treaty provisions. You agree
									to comply with all copyright laws worldwide in your use of this Site and to prevent any unauthorized copying of the Materials. Except as
									expressly provided herein, TATA POWER does not grant any express or implied right to you under any patents, trademarks, copyrights or trade
									secret information.</html:li>
							</html:ul>
							<html:p>
								The information, material or services included in or available through this site may include inaccuracies or typographical errors. Changes
								are periodically made to the site/services and to the information therein. TATA POWER and/or its respective suppliers may make improvements
								and/or changes in the site/services at any time.
							</html:p>
							<html:p>
								While we have made every effort to ensure the accuracy and clarity of the information presented in this site, however TATA POWER cannot be
								held liable for any errors or inconsistencies. Advice received via this site should not be relied upon for personal, medical, legal, and
								financial or any decisions and you should consult an appropriate professional for specific advice tailored to your situation. No information
								on this site shall constitute an invitation to invest in TATA POWER or any of its affiliates. Neither TATA POWER nor their officers,
								employees or agents shall be liable for any loss, damage or expense arising out of any access to or use of this site or any site linked to
								it, including, without limitation, any loss of profit, indirect, incidental or consequential loss.
							</html:p>
							<html:p>
								You specifically agree that TATA POWER shall not be responsible for unauthorized access to or alteration of your transmissions or data, any
								material or data sent or received or not sent or received, or any transactions entered into through this site. You specifically agree that
								TATA POWER is not responsible or liable for any threatening, defamatory, obscene, offensive or illegal content or conduct of any other party
								or any infringement of another's rights, including intellectual property rights. You specifically agree that TATA POWER is not responsible
								for any content sent using and/or included in this site by any third party.
							</html:p>
							<html:p>
								The linked sites are not under our control and we are not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked
								site, or any changes or updates to such sites. We are providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does
								not imply endorsement by us of the site.
							</html:p>
							<html:p>
								In no event shall TATA POWER and/or its suppliers be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special, consequential damages
								or any damages whatsoever including, without limitation, damages for loss of use, data or profits, arising out of or in any way connected
								with the use or performance of this site/services, with the delay or inability to use this site/services or related services, the provision
								of or failure to provide services, or for any information, products, services and material obtained through this site, or otherwise arising
								out of the use of this site/services, whether based on contract, tort, negligence, strict liability or otherwise, even if TATA POWER or any
								of its suppliers has been advised of the possibility of damages. If you are dissatisfied with any portion of this site / services, or with
								any of these terms of use, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using this site / services. The foregoing are subject to the
								laws of the Republic of India and the courts in Mumbai, India shall have the exclusive jurisdiction on any dispute that may arise out of the
								use of this site.
							</html:p>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
					<core:Fragment fragmentName="tatapower.dev.fragments.Main.Footer" type="XML"/>
				</content>
			</Page>
		</pages>
	</App>
</mvc:View>