<core:FragmentDefinition xmlns="sap.m" xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:u="sap.ui.unified" xmlns:tnt="sap.tnt" height="100%"
	xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<Panel >
		<content>
			<Panel>
				<html:div class="container-fluid">
					<html:div class="go-green_intro">
						<html:div class="row intro_head">
							<html:div class="col-xs-12">
								<html:div class="grn_cor border_rad_icon">
									<html:div class="row icon_row_flex">
										<html:div class="col-xs-2">
											<html:image src="images/icon_green_corn.png" alt="icon_green_corn" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
										</html:div>
										<html:div class="col-xs-10">
											<html:h4>Green Buildings</html:h4>
										</html:div>
									</html:div>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
					<html:div class="green_build_desc">
						<html:p class="gbd_head text-center">
							"A green building is one which uses less water, optimises energy efficiency, conserves natural resources, generates less waste and provides
							healthier spaces for occupants, as compared to a conventional building."
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							The construction industry is one of the largest economic activities contributing to India's development. India has been witnessing
							tremendous growth in building and construction sector for the past 5 years.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							The Indian Green Building Council (IGBC) was formed in the year 2001 to usher in a green building movement. A Green home can have tremendous
							benefits, both tangible and intangible. The immediate and most tangible benefit is in the reduction in water and operating energy costs
							right from day one, during the entire life cycle of the building. The intangible benefits are enhanced air quality, excellent day lighting,
							health &amp; wellbeing of the occupants, conservation of scarce national resources, enhance marketability for the project. LEED-INDIA for
							new construction and major renovations is a green building rating system that helps to guide and design high-performance commercial
							buildings.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							The Energy Conservation Building Code (ECBC) was launched in May 2007 by the Hon'ble Minister of Power, and is presently in vogue on
							voluntary basis.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							The ECBC sets minimum energy standards for new commercial buildings having a connected load of 500kW or contract demand of 600 kVA. BEE is
							promoting the implementation of energy efficiency measures in existing buildings through Energy Service Companies (ESCOs) which provide an
							innovative business model through which the energy-saving potential in existing building can be captured and the risk faced by building
							owner can also be addressed.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							IGBC and ECBC encourage designers to develop low Carbon-foot-print designs related to following attributes.
						</html:p>
						<html:ul class="inti_list">
							<html:li>Site Planning.</html:li>
							<html:li>Environmental Architecture.</html:li>
							<html:li>Energy efficient building materials.</html:li>
							<html:li>Innovative space and water heating/cooling techniques.</html:li>
							<html:li>Water conservation and recycling.</html:li>
						</html:ul>
						<html:p>
							The Indian Bureau of Energy Efficiency has launched the Energy Conservation Building Codes for 5 climate zones in India. ECBC defines
							performance parameters of the built commercial space (private development and public buildings).
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							For more information, we encourage you to visit following sites:
							<html:span><html:a href="http://www.bee-india.nic.in/" target="_blank" title="Bee India">http://www.bee-india.nic.in/</html:a></html:span>
							<html:span><html:a href="https://igbc.in/igbc/" target="_blank" title="IGBC">https://igbc.in/igbc/</html:a></html:span>
						</html:p>
					</html:div>
				</html:div>
			</Panel>
		</content>
	</Panel>
</core:FragmentDefinition>