<core:FragmentDefinition xmlns="sap.m" xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:u="sap.ui.unified" xmlns:tnt="sap.tnt" height="100%"
	xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<Panel >
		<content>
			<Panel>
				<html:div class="container-fluid">
					<html:div class="go-green_intro">
						<html:div class="row intro_head">
							<html:div class="col-xs-12">
								<html:div class="grn_cor border_rad_icon">
									<html:div class="row icon_row_flex">
										<html:div class="col-xs-2">
											<html:image src="images/icon_green_corn.png" alt="icon_green_corn" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
										</html:div>
										<html:div class="col-xs-10">
											<html:h4>Energy Efficient Devices</html:h4>
										</html:div>
									</html:div>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
					<html:div class="green_build_desc">
						<html:p>
							Switching to energy efficient devices will help the consumer to reduce their electricity bills. The Government of India set up Bureau of
							Energy Efficiency (BEE) on 1st March 2002 under the provisions of the Energy Conservation Act, 2001. BEE develops minimum energy performance
							standards and labelling (S&amp;L) design for equipment and appliances.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							BEE's S&amp;L programme for household electrical appliances aims at providing information on energy performance of appliances based on the
							standards issued by BEE so that the consumers can make informed decisions while purchasing appliances. Consumer can make star rating as
							important criteria in the selection of a model which helps to reduce the energy consumption of appliance without diminishing the services it
							provides to consumers. The use of energy efficient product will help to shift the market towards greener products.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							Under the S&amp;L scheme which was launched by BEE there are four mandatory and rest are voluntary products. The four products that are
							under the mandatory labelling are frost free refrigerator, room air conditioner, TFL (Tubular Fluorescent Lamp) and distribution
							transformer. The other products under the voluntary labelling are direct cool refrigerator, general purpose induction motor, mono set pumps,
							open well pump sets, submersible pump sets, ceiling fan, domestic gas stoves, stationary storage type water heater, colour television and
							washing machine.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							Tata Power also promotes 5 star energy efficient products through Demand Side Management programs. To know more about these programme please
							log on to,
							<html:strong>"My Mumbai Green Mumbai"</html:strong>
							initiative by Tata Power.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							For more information on star rating products kindly visit to following sites:
							<html:span>
								<html:a href="http://www.bee-india.nic.in/" target="_blank" title="Bee India">http://www.bee-india.nic.in/</html:a>
							</html:span>
							<html:span>
								<html:a href="http://www.saveenergy.co.in/" target="_blank" title="Save Energy">http://www.saveenergy.co.in/</html:a>
							</html:span>
						</html:p>
					</html:div>
				</html:div>
			</Panel>
		</content>
	</Panel>
</core:FragmentDefinition>