<core:FragmentDefinition xmlns="sap.m" xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:u="sap.ui.unified" xmlns:tnt="sap.tnt" height="100%"
	xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<Panel >
		<content>
			<Panel>
				<html:div class="container-fluid padding_bottom">
					<html:div class="go-green_intro">
						<html:div class="row intro_head">
							<html:div class="col-xs-12">
								<html:div class="knw_cen_bg border_rad_icon">
									<html:div class="row icon_row_flex">
										<html:div class="col-xs-2">
											<html:image src="images/icon_knowledge.png" alt="icon_knowledge" class="img-responsive"></html:image>
										</html:div>
										<html:div class="col-xs-10">
											<html:h4>Safety Guidelines</html:h4>
										</html:div>
									</html:div>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
						</html:div>
						<html:div class="safety_guide_info">
							<html:p>
								Electricity is one of the greatest inventions, which has dramatically changed our life style. It is our best friend and always at our
								command. But at the same time it has to be handled carefully. It can also be dangerous to life and can cause injuries or property damage or
								both. Hence it is essential to take all precautions in proper use of electrical equipment.
							</html:p>
						</html:div>
						<html:div class="safety_guide_req">
							<html:div class="row">
								<html:div class="col-sm-6">
									<html:h5>You are requested to :</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="blue_bullet_list">
										<html:li>Treat all circuits as LIVE until they are confirmed to be DEAD, after testing.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use fuse wire of the correct size and capacity without a joint.</html:li>
										<html:li>Place a main switch that is easily accessible for turning off the supply in case of an emergency.</html:li>
										<html:li>Ensure that fuses are installed only on the phase wires.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use E.L.C.B. (Earth Leakage Circuit Breaker) with the main switch for added personal safety.</html:li>
										<html:li>Allow only qualified persons / licensed electricians to carry out electrical repairs.</html:li>
										<html:li>Preferably use ISI marked / certified electrical appliances / equipment / materials.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use electrical cables and equipment of adequate capacity and proper insulation.</html:li>
										<html:li>Ensure that all appliances / equipment are provided with a 3-pin plug and socket.</html:li>
										<html:li>Ensure outer metal parts of the appliances / equipment are effectively earthed.</html:li>
										<html:li>Always use only an insulated wire for Neutral.</html:li>
										<html:li>Always use a separate wire for Earthing.</html:li>
										<html:li>Pull out the supply end first while removing a fuse and put in the supply end in the last while inserting it.</html:li>
										<html:li>Before replacing a lamp ensure that the supply is turned off.</html:li>
										<html:li>Ensure that earthing to electrical installations be done with a copper wire / plate / rod and make sure there are no paint or
											insulating materials on the earthing terminal.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use an adequate capacity extension box for plugging in more than one equipment.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use only one plug in a socket.</html:li>
										<html:li>Turn off the supply immediately in case of a short circuit / fire in or near electrical appliances.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use only CO2 or Dry Chemical Powder extinguishers for dousing electrical fire.</html:li>
										<html:li>Always wear dry rubber footwear / gloves while handling electrical appliances. Also stand on a rubber mat / dry wooden plank.</html:li>
										<html:li>Turn off the supply immediately in case of an electrical accident. Insulate yourself on a dry board / insulating material before
											removing the person in contact with the live part. Immediately call for a doctor and continue to give artificial respiration till medical
											assistance arrives.</html:li>
										<html:li>Educate children on the dangers of mishandling electrical connections, equipment and appliances. Cover the holes of sockets which
											are not in use, easily reachable by children.
										</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
								<html:div class="col-sm-6">
									<html:h5>You are requested not to :</html:h5>
									<html:ul class="red_bullet_list">
										<html:li>Make any temporary joints in the wiring, especially without proper insulation.</html:li>
										<html:li>Insert wires directly into the plug socket without a matching plug pin, even if only on a temporary basis.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use any appliances without proper earthing.</html:li>
										<html:li>Install a fuse on the neutral circuit.</html:li>
										<html:li>Overload the wires by using multiple appliances from a single plug socket.</html:li>
										<html:li>Replace a fuse unless the fault is detected and rectified.</html:li>
										<html:li>Provide a higher size fuse wire than the prescribed size.</html:li>
										<html:li>Touch a bare wire, i.e. without insulation. It may be LIVE.</html:li>
										<html:li>Allow water to enter your electrical appliances while cleaning them.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use wet hands to turn ON or turn OFF a switch.</html:li>
										<html:li>Plug in any appliances when the switch is ON.</html:li>
										<html:li>Touch a person who is in contact with a live circuit.</html:li>
										<html:li>Turn ON a switch unless the plug is completely inserted.</html:li>
										<html:li>Use water for extinguishing fires caused due to electricity or in the vicinity of electrical equipment.</html:li>
										<html:li>Allow children to play with sockets, plugs, wires and other electrical appliances.</html:li>
									</html:ul>
								</html:div>
							</html:div>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
				</html:div>
			</Panel>
		</content>
	</Panel>
</core:FragmentDefinition>