<core:FragmentDefinition xmlns="sap.m" xmlns:core="sap.ui.core" xmlns:u="sap.ui.unified" xmlns:tnt="sap.tnt" height="100%"
	xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<Panel >
		<content>
			<Panel>
				<html:div class="container-fluid">
					<html:div class="go-green_intro">
						<html:div class="intro_head">
							<html:h4>About Tata Power Consumer Portal</html:h4>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
					<html:div class="about_desc">
						<html:p>
							Welcome to Tata Power Consumer Care Portal. We at Tata Power, have been constantly striving to innovate and provide services to exceed
							Consumer expectations.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							Through this portal, we are attempting to reach out to all our Consumers who will find it convenient to seek information and do meaningful
							transactions. The design and content of this portal has been done keeping Consumers’ convenience and needs in mind. We hope you find it a
							worthwhile experience and the navigation user friendly.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							Please get yourself registered at once and experience the difference!
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							We value your suggestions. So, do not hesitate to give your candid feedback ! We look forward to hearing from you!
						</html:p>
					</html:div>
					<html:div class="about_read_more">
						<html:p>
							Recognised as India’s largest private sector power utility, with a reputation for trustworthiness, built up over nearly nine decades, Tata
							Power surges ahead into yet another year with plans of sustained growth, greater value to consumer and reliable power supply.
						</html:p>
						<html:p>
							Led by a powerful vision, Tata Power pioneered the generation of electricity in India. It has now successfully served the Mumbai consumers
							for over ninety years and has spread its footprints across the nation. Today, it is the country’s largest private player in the sector.
							Apart from Mumbai and Delhi, the company has generation capacities in Jojobera, Jharkhand and Karnataka.
						</html:p>
						<html:div class="read_more_link">
							<html:a href="https://www.tatapower.com/" title="Read More" target="_blank">Read More</html:a>
						</html:div>
					</html:div>
				</html:div>
			</Panel>
		</content>
	</Panel>
</core:FragmentDefinition>